SHREYAS PRAKASH BHAT

Newark, NJ 9738106808 sp2677@njit.edu

https://shreyasarthur.github.io/MyPortfolio/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shreyas-prakash-bhat/

Enthusiast Master s Student specializing in Computer Science who is a team player with a can-do attitude. A creative thinker who can handle difficult situations patiently and curious to learn and master new technologies.

EDUCATION

2019 - Present	Master's in Computer Science New Jersey Institute of Technology, Newark, NJ	Current CGPA: 3.6/4
2015 – 2019	B.E in Computer Science & Engineering Jyothy Institute of Technology, Bangalore, Karnata	CGPA: 6.9/10 (3.25/4)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Python Developer - Data Scientist (05/2020 to Present)

New Jersey Institute of Technology, Newark, NJ

I was responsible for developing models that create colorful urban plans from just black and white scratches using Generative adversarial networks. The designers feed the models with the initial black and white scratches and then models convert those scratches to colorful urban plans saving a lot of money and time for the planners.

Technologies Used: Python, Tensorflow, Cuda, CuDNN and Pytorch

Web Developer Intern (04/2018 to 06/2018)

JIT Bangalore, India

I was in the team that was responsible for the front end of the system. I led the effort to build the system enabling the customer to search for airline companies, flights on a specified date, choose a flight based on the details such as flight no, name, price and duration of journey, reservation of flight and cancellation of reservation.

Technologies Used: Java, JavaScript, JDBC, HTML/CSS and MySQL.

SKILLS

My Skill-set Include: Python, Tensorflow, Cuda, CuDNN, PyTorch, Pandas, Numpy, MySQL, Java, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, PHP and PHPMyAdmin

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Abnormal Events Detection in Surveillance Systems Mar 2018 – Jun 2019

This project allows monitoring of abnormal events in real-time and notifies the security team if such events are detected. This reduces the strenuous task of going through the entire CCTV footage. The algorithm used in the project is Convolutional neural network and the dataset used is UCF dataset. We train the neural network through abnormal, anomalous and normal videos and with clipping them as video segments and extracting the features.

 Programming technologies and libraries used were Python, Tensorflow, Keras, Theanos, Numpy and Pandas.

Yelp Plus Aug 2019 – Dec 2019

I was responsible for the front end of the android app called yelp plus which is very similar to yelp and added few useful features like Filter reviews by ratings, time, most helpful, Detailed star ranking, Rank business by product, service, ambience etc.

Programming Technologies that were used are Java, JSP and MongoDB.

MovieSite Dec 2018

This Website is a MovieSite which gives information about recent movies. It is user-friendly and easy to access for the Users and acts as a bridge connection between the user and the world of movies. This work is an initial exploration of how a user is able to get the information about movies from various fields like Sandalwood, Hollywood, Bollywood.

• Programming Technologies used were HTML, CSS, PHP and PHPMyAdmin.

PUBLICATIONS AND VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Abnormal Events Detection in Surveillance Systems, Jun 2019 www.academia.edu/40286517/Abnormal_Events_Detection_in_Surveillance_Systems

Detection of Abnormal Events, Mar 2018 http://ijiet.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/11.pdf

Donated and volunteered in #runforcoorg 5K cross county marathon event organized by Rotary Club.